

# HUYNH THI KIM OANH

## **ABOUT ME**

I am an Junior Product Analyst with less than 1 year in Data Analyst but having 5 years of experience in Marketing and Business background.

My goal in 3 years is become a Full Stack Data - Who is able to be Data Engineer and Data Analyst, specific in Marketing and Product field.

# CONTACT INFO

+84\*\*\*\*\*\*\*

@oanh-huynh-3011

oanhhuynh1130@gmail.com

Oistrict 1, Ho Chi Minh City

## **EDUCATION**

# University of Economy in Ho Chi Minh city

Bachelor of Marketing - 2019

# DigitalMarketer

- Digital Marketing Mastery 2021
- Content Marketing Mastery 2020
- Social Media Mastery 2021

## MindX

Data Analysis - 2023

## **WORK EXPERIENCES**

## **GLINTS**

Junior Product Analyst | Jul 2023 - Present · 6 mos

- Created report dashboard on Metabase, Looker Studio, Google Sheet to manage performance and direct marketing effort
- Collaborated with DE to build User flow and track all user steps in Growth model
- Collected and monitored competitor's data with DE

Senior SEO specialist | Oct 2021 - Jun 2023 · 1 yr 9 mos

- Created, implemented, and reported on SEO strategies.
- Handled advanced SEO research and analysis to assist the SEO team in the decision-making process.

#### **HOBY**

Vice President of Marketing  $\mid$  Sep 2019 - Nov 2021  $\cdot$  2 yrs 3 mos

- Conducted research & develope new products
- Researched & identified potential customer profiles
- Planned and executed marketing development channels, including Website, Facebook, YouTube, Shopee, and PBN
- Implemented SEO
- Managed inventory
- · Provided customer support

# NHÀ DIGI

Head of SEO | Aug 2020 - Aug 2021 · 1 yr 1 mo

- Researched and analyzed the target audience for each project
- Planned and managed SEO website projects with a focus on user experience
- Researched new SEO techniques and established working processes
- Monitored and optimized the conversion rate for clients

## **GTV SEO**

SEO Manager | Aug 2018 - Nov 2019 · 1 yr 4 mos

- Planned, managed, and implemented over 10 SEO projects across different industries and sizes.
- · Lead and train a team of 7 members
- Research new SEO techniques and establish working processes
- Collaborate with the Marketing department to connect with and support clients

# **PROJECTS**

# **#1: JOB SUPPLY & DEMAND DASHBOARD**

- Goal: Determine the gap between supply candidate and demand job. Find out how much users and jobs we need more to drive marketing effort.
- Description: Tracking weekly job and user metrics, calculate new metrics to give actionables for the team
- Team size: 1
- Responsibilities:
  - Conducted user research for user satisfaction.
  - Collected data by SQL and created metrics from data lake
  - Brainstormed ideas for threshold and calculation fomular with CTO
  - Setup report and monitored weekly
- Git link

# **#2: SALARY PREDICTION MODEL**

- Goal: Provide to Employer using job platform a tool to predict salary range while hiring.
- Description: Using Gradient Boosting model and job platform's data and to predict the suitable salary range for a role.
- Team size: 1
- Responsibilities:
  - Collected data by SQL and created metrics from data lake
  - Data pre-processing, Standardlize data, Removed outlier using IQR EDA
  - Evaluated model
- Git link

## SKILLS

- ✓ HTML, CSS, PHP
- ✓ SQL, Python
- English: Intermediate
- ✓ Proficient in Photoshop, Canva
- ✓ SEO
- ✓ Training
- Proficient in using Using SEO
   Tools: Screaming frog, Ahrefs,
   Website auditor, Lumar,...
- Building dashboard with Looker Studio, Metabase, Power BI

# REFERENCES

🖈 Đỗ Hoàng Phúc - CEO at Hoby & Nhà Digi

Phone: +84 \*\*\*\*\*\*\*
Email: dohoang\*\*\*\*\*@gmail.com

★ Andreas Budiman - SEO Manager at Glints

Phone: +62 \*\*\*\*\*\*\*\*\*\*\*\*\*\*\*\*\*\*\*
Email: andr\*\*\*\*\*\*\*\*@gmail.com